System Dynamic Society; Records ua435
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Conferences, 1976-2018
  - Washington, DC, 2011 July 24-2011 July 28
    - Papers, 2011 July 24-2011 July 28
      - Schoenberg, William, "How best to present model structure to decision makers? An experimental study of the effectiveness of the Forio model explorer", 2011 July 24-2011 July 28
      - Seker, Oylum with Yaman Barlas, "Modeling the Dynamics of Thyroid Hormones and Related Disorders (Lupina Award Winner)", 2011 July 24-2011 July 28
      - Silva, Vanina with Antonio Coelho and Antonio Novaes, "The role of collaboration through manufactured goods' exportation process under System Dynamics analysis", 2011 July 24-2011 July 28
      - Simonelli, James, "A System Dynamics Perspective on Applying a New Energy Efficiency Metric for Data Centers", 2011 July 24-2011 July 28
      - Skarin, Bruce, "Distributed Group Problem Solving", 2011 July 24-2011 July 28
      - Skribans, Valerijs, "Development of System Dynamic Model of Latvia's Economic Integration in the EU", 2011 July 24-2011 July 28
      - Stave, Krystyna with Benjamin Jurand and Heather Skaza, "Description and demonstration of a simulation learning environment for discovery learning about simple accumulations", 2011 July 24-2011 July 28
      - Stave, Krystyna with Heather Skaza and Benjamin Jurand, "Using Simulations for Discovery Learning about Environmental Accumulations", 2011 July 24-2011 July 28
      - Steverink, Bart with Cornelia van Daalen, "The Dutch Taxation on Airline Tickets: A system dynamics approach to model airport choice", 2011 July 24-2011 July 28
      - Strohhecker, Jürgen, "Illuminating the Logic of Stock Management Failure – How Much Does the (Mis)Understanding of Accumulation Explain?", 2011 July 24-2011 July 28
      - Struben, Jeroen with Charles Gauvin, "Language Evolution in Québec: Network effects and clustering", 2011 July 24-2011 July 28
      - Struben, Jeroen with Derek Chan, "Non-communicable Disease Dynamics and Prevention: Dynamics of Nutritious Food Market Transformation Initiatives", 2011 July 24-2011 July 28
      - Struben, Jeroen with John Sterman, "Strategies for Transportation Electrification: Overcoming Thresholds and Overly Optimistic Forecasts", 2011 July 24-2011 July 28
      - Susta, Marek with Gustav Bizik, "Human Stress Response from the System Dynamics Point of View", 2011 July 24-2011 July 28
      - Tanyolac, Togay with Hakan Yasarcan, "A Soft Landing Model and a Mass-Spring Damper Based Control Heuristic", 2011 July 24-2011 July 28
      - Tasrif, Muhammad with Ina Juniarti, "A Dynamic View on Knowledge Development: A Case of Industrial Aerospace Supply Chain Development in Indonesia", 2011 July 24-2011 July 28
      - Thompson, James with Crystal Riley and David Matchar, "System Dynamics of Diminishing Family Size on Living Arrangements of Singaporeans with Ageing-related Dementia", 2011 July 24-2011 July 28
      - Tian, Yuan with Nathaniel Osgood, "Comparison between Individual-based and Aggregate Models in the Context of Tuberculosis Transmission", 2011 July 24-2011 July 28
      - Tignor, Warren, "Agile Essence", 2011 July 24-2011 July 28
      - Ullah, Muhammad with Tiru Arthanari, "Using a Qualitative System Dynamics Approach to Investigate Perception of Corruption", 2011 July 24-2011 July 28
      - Ulli-Beer, Silvia, "How does the Multi-Level Perspective help to conceptualize a System Dynamics analysis of a specific transition challenge?", 2011 July 24-2011 July 28
      - Uriona Maldonado, Mauricio with Gregorio Varvakis, "Analyzing Training Programs from a KM perspective: A System Dynamics model", 2011 July 24-2011 July 28
      - Uzmez, Beril with Necati Aras and Yaman Barlas, "Strategic Analysis of Product Recovery Management by Using System Dynamics Approach", 2011 July 24-2011 July 28
      - Venkateswaran, Jayendran with Kaushik Margabandu, D. Bijulal and Nandyala Hemachandra, "Simulation based Analysis of Service Levels in Stable Production-Inventory Systems", 2011 July 24-2011 July 28
      - Viejo Garcia, Pablo with Jose Gonzalez, Oscar Barambones and Enrique Kremers, "Quantitative systems dynamics: Comparison of modeling techniques for the simulation of electro-mechanical systems", 2011 July 24-2011 July 28
      - Villa, Sebastian with Paulo Goncalves and Santiago Arango, "Retailer's Order Decisions under Delays: System Dynamics and Experimental Results", 2011 July 24-2011 July 28
      - Villaseñor, Roberto, "System Dynamics in Reverse Logistics Processes", 2011 July 24-2011 July 28
      - Voyer, John with Troy Goddu, Cade Blackburn and Brian Sprague, "A System Dynamics Examination of the Use of Performance Enhancing Drugs", 2011 July 24-2011 July 28
      - Wahba, Khaled, "The Egyptian Revolution 2011: The Fall of the Virtual Wall - The Revolution Systems Thinking Archetype", 2011 July 24-2011 July 28
      - Walker, Rod with Wayne Wakeland, "Calibration of Complex System Dynamics Models: A Practitioner's Report", 2011 July 24-2011 July 28
      - Wang, Hsiao-Lin with Yu-Feng Ho and Ching-I Wu, "Dynamics Model of Eco-Security Surveillance System for the Tamsui River in Taipei City", 2011 July 24-2011 July 28
      - Wheat, David with Lili Shi, "Exploratory Policy Design", 2011 July 24-2011 July 28
      - Woodlock, Don, "Time to Bite the Hand that Feeds You", 2011 July 24-2011 July 28
      - Wunderlich, Philipp with Andreas Groessler, "Raising Implementation Effectiveness of Innovations by Considering Structural Aspects of Organizations", 2011 July 24-2011 July 28
      - Xu, Zhao, "Application of System Dynamics model and GIS in sustainability assessment of urban residential development", 2011 July 24-2011 July 28
      - Yamaguchi, Kaoru, "Workings of A Public Money System of Open Macroeconomies - Modeling the American Monetary Act Completed", 2011 July 24-2011 July 28
      - Yamashita, Takayuki, "A System Dynamics Approach to the Regional Macro-economic Model", 2011 July 24-2011 July 28
      - Yasarcan, Hakan, "Information Sharing in Supply Chains: A Systemic Approach", 2011 July 24-2011 July 28
      - Yearworth, Michael with Daniel Schien, Chris Preist and Paul Shabajee, "Systems Modelling of New Media Services", 2011 July 24-2011 July 28
      - Yucel, Gönenç with Erik Pruyt, "Energy Transition in The Dutch Dwelling Stock: Exploring the Extent of Inertia Against Change", 2011 July 24-2011 July 28
      - Yucel, Gönenç with Cornelia van Daalen, "A Simulation-based Analysis of Transition Pathways for the Dutch Electricity System", 2011 July 24-2011 July 28
      - Zagonel, Aldo with Mohammad Mojtahedzadeh, George Richardson, Nancy Brodsky, Theresa Brown, Stephen Conrad and Robert Glass, "Developing a theory of the societal lifecycle of cigarette smoking: Explaining & anticipating trends using information feedback", 2011 July 24-2011 July 28
      - Zawadzki, Tomasz with Radostaw Pytlak, "Extending System Dynamics approach to higher index DAE's", 2011 July 24-2011 July 28
      - Zimmermann, Nicole, "Mechanisms of consumer boycotts: Evidence from the Nestlé infant food controversy", 2011 July 24-2011 July 28
      - Dahan, Mariana, "Innovating Through the Crisis: System Dynamics Modeling Applied to International Development Work and World Bank Operations", 2011 July 24-2011 July 28
      - Dykes, Katherine, "Student Chapter Poster Presentation and Annual Meeting", 2011 July 24-2011 July 28
      - Kennedy, Michael with Carol Frances, "Education Special Interest Group Poster Presentation, Roundtable and Annual Meeting", 2011 July 24-2011 July 28
      - Lychkina, Natalya, "Russian Chapter Poster Presentation", 2011 July 24-2011 July 28
      - Lyneis, James, "System Dynamics Applications Award Announcement and Introduction of Winner", 2011 July 24-2011 July 28
      - Rahn, R. Joel, "Dana Meadows Award Announcement", 2011 July 24-2011 July 28
      - Rogers, James with Edward Gallaher, "Biophysical Special Interest Group (Proposed) - A Planning Meeting", 2011 July 24-2011 July 28
      - Schaffernicht, Martin with Stefan Groesser, "Peer Review Dialog Meeting", 2011 July 24-2011 July 28
      - Strohhecker, Jürgen, "German Chapter Poster Presentation", 2011 July 24-2011 July 28
    - Sponsor Notes, 2011 July 24-2011 July 28
  - Seoul, Korea, 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
    - Conference Website, 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
    - Sessions by Thread, 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
    - Abstract Proceedings, 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
    - Papers, 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Abdelgawad, Ahmed Abdeltawab with Mikael Snaprud and John Krogstie, "Accessibility of Norwegian Municipalities Websites: A Qualitative System Dynamics Approach", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Abdollahzadeh, Alireza with Hossein Rahdari, Fariba Seyed Jafar Rangraz, Jafar Pashami and Nazanin Karimi, "Effects of Government Intervention in Interest Rates: Case of Iran", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Adeniran, Ezekiel, "A System Dynamics Strategic Planning Model for a Municipal Water Supply Scheme", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Ahn, Yoo-Jeong with Man-Hyung Lee, "How to Guarantee Effectiveness of National Rental Housing Policies Applying SD Approaches?: Focused on Residential Development", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Akbarzadeh Khorshidi, Hadi with Marzieh Soltanolkottabi, "Hegelian Philosophy and System Dynamics", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Akpinar, Yesim Atag with Ali Saysel, "A Dynamic Simulation Model of Carbon Circulation and Methane Feedbacks in Anthropogenic Climate Change", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - An, Lianjun with Ching-Hua Chen-Ritzo, "Integrated Healthcare Delivery and Health Insurance Models for Studying Emergency Department Utilization", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - An, Lianjun with Young Lee, "Modeling Propagation of Infectious Disease as a Connected Network", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Andersen, David with George Richardson, "Improvised Facilitation: A Third Leg on the Group Model Building Stool", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Ansah, John, "Modeling the Dynamics of Poverty Trap and Debt Accumulation", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Ansah, John, "Negotiating Fiscal Sustainability against Socio-Economic Development: A Model-Based Policy Analysis", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Ansah, John, "The Dynamics of Public Indebtedness in Ghana", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Armenia, Stefano with Fabrizio Baldoni, Diego Falsini and Emanuele Taibi, "A System Dynamics Energy Model for a Sustainable Transportation System", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Atefi, Yashar with Farzad Minooei and Rambod Dargahi, "Housing Affordability: A study of real estate market in Iran", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Bajracharya, Arun, "Systems Thinking, Dependent Co-Arising and Mental Model in Decision Making", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Bayer, Steffen with Timothy Bolt, Maria Kapsali and Sally Brailsford, "The social role of simulation models", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Bier, Asmeret with Michael Bernard, George Backus and Richard Hills, "Political Dynamics Determined by Interactions Between Political Leaders and Voters", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Bilusich, Daniel with Fred Bowden and Svetoslav Gaidow, "Influence Diagram Supporting the Implementation of Adaptive Campaigning", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Bisilkas, Marios, "Adaptation on Rugged Landscapes: Competitive Strategies in the Presence of a Common Objective", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Borshchev, Andrei, "Getting Started with AnyLogic - a Multi-Method Simulation Modeling Tool", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Brammer, Richard with Bernd Viehweger, "The Player Number Growth in Online Social Games", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Buendia, Fernando, "Self-Organizing Market Structures, System Dynamics, and Urn Theory", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Bull, Oscar, "System Dynamics Applied to Combat Models (Lanchester Laws)", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Calhoun, Annaliese with Peter Hovmand, David Andersen, George Richardson, Timothy Hower and Etiënne Rouwette, "Scriptapedia: A Digital Commons for Documenting and Sharing Group Model Building Scripts", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Carhart, Neil with Michael Yearworth, "The Use of Group Model Building for Analysing Event Causality within the Nuclear Industry", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Cavana, Robert with Thomas Adams, "A Qualitative System Dynamics Analysis of the Effects of an Emissions Trading Scheme on the New Zealand Forestry Value Chain", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Ceresia, Francesco with Giovan Battista Montemaggiore, "Applying the Goal Setting Practice in the Dynamic Balance Scorecard Learning and Growth Perspective", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Chahal, Kirandeep with Tillal Eldabi, "A generic framework for hybrid simulation in healthcare", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Chaim, Ricardo with Rosalvo Streit, "A platform to produce hybrid models in order to manage risks and uncertainties on financial and actuarial organizations", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Chaim, Ricardo, "Modeling Transportation Public - Private Partnerships", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Chang, Chao-Ching, "Ambidextrous Effects of Relational-specific Investments in the OEM Transactions", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Chateau, Pierre-Alexandre, "A system dynamics model for marine cage aquaculture", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Chen, Jian Hung with Yijen Chen, "Modeling the Evolution of Public Industry R&D Institute - the Case of ITRI", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Cofiel, Luciana with Guilherme Zammar, Amrapali Zaveri, Jatin Shah, Elias Cesar Araujo de Carvalho, Meredith Nahm, Gustavo Kesselring and Ricardo Pietrobon, "A system dynamics analysis to determine willingness to wait and pay for inclusion of data standards in clinical research", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Colombo, Gianluca with M. Vincenzo Piantedosi, "Roles Differentiation in Family Firms Succession: The Impact of Private banking and Private Equity", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Conner, Daniel with Allison Deal, Gautam Yadama and Kumar Rupam, "The Livelihood-Energy-Conservation Nexus: Intervention strategies to promote conservation in forest villages", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Cumenal, Didier, "How the concept of organisational value highlights corporate performance drivers", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Dai, Shanshan with Lan Hai Li and Xu Honggang, "The system dynamic study of regional development of Manas Basin Under the constraints of water resources", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Dangerfield, Brian with Norhaslinda Zainal Abidin, "Towards a model-based Tool for Evaluating Population-level Interventions against Childhood Obesity", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Dave, Ashka with Colleen Kinneen and Kimberly Newcomer, "Lake to Puddle: A System Dynamics Approach to Social, Economic, and Environmental Consequences of Water Use in Udaipur, India", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Derwisch, Sebastian with Birgit Kopainsky, "Dynamics of Enforcement and Infringement of Intellectual Property Rights and Implications for Innovation Incentives", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Di Giulio, Vincenzo with Stefania Migliavacca, "Bottom-up and top-down approaches in energy efficiency estimation.", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Diaz Pabon, Fabio with Catherine Espinoza, Martha Namen Leon, Maria Palacio and Rafael Cuervo, "Humanitarian Crisis: when Supply Chain really matters", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Dykes, Katherine with John Sterman, "Boom and Bust Cycles in Wind Energy Diffusion Due to Inconsistency and Short-term Bias in National Energy Policies", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Falihi Pirbasti, Nemat with Marzieh Hanjani, "The study of inflation effects on Iran Large Industrial Workshops profit: combiniaion of system dynamics and econometrics", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Flachskampf, Paul with Klaus Henning, "Systemic strategy development and implementation using the example of a lead brokerage financial service provider", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Ford, Andrew, "Greening the Economy with New Markets: Lessons from System Dynamics Simulation of Energy and Environmental Markets", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Garzia, Carmine, "The Process of Strategic Innovation: A System Dynamics Approach", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - GhanbarTehrani, Nasim, "Modeling Dynamics of gaining expertise in a call center", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Goh, Yang Miang with Peter Love and Daniel Lo, "System Dynamics Analysis of Organizational Accidents: A Review of Current Approaches", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Golnam, Arash with Ann van Ackere and Alain Wegmann, "Integrating System Dynamics and Enterprise Modeling to Address Dynamic and Structural Complexities of Choice Situations", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Goncalves, Paulo with Santiago Arango Aramburo, "Supplier Capacity Decisions Under Retailer Competition and Delays: Theoretical and Experimental Results", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Groessler, Andreas, "Rats, Black Swans, and Personal Careers - an Investigation of "Go with the flow" and "Deviate from common behaviour" Strategies", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Hayward, John, "Church Growth via Enthusiasts and Renewal", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Hekimoglu, Mustafa, "Sensitivity Analysis of Oscillatory System Dynamics Models", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Hekimoglu, Mustafa with Yaman Barlas, "Sensitivity Analysis of System Dynamics Models by Behavior Pattern Measures", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Herdem, Canan with Hakan Yasarcan, "Dynamics of Glucose-Insulin Regulation: Insulin Injection Regime for Patients with Diabetes Type I", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Ho, Yu-Feng with Hsiao-Lin Wang and Cheng-Chih Liu, "Dynamics Model of Housing Market Surveillance System for Taichung City", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Honggang, Xu with Shanshan Dai, "Exploring Sustainable Policies for Xidi, the World Heritage Village", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Hovmand, Peter, "Better Healthcare through Better Design of Healthcare Research and Development", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Hovmand, Peter with Gautam Yadama, Nishesh Chalise, Annaliese Calhoun and Daniel Conner, "Combining Group Model Building and Participatory Rural Appraisal in Southeast Rural India", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Hsueh, Joe, "What Can Formal Modeling Add to Qualitative Systems Thinking? A Simulation Model of the Shift the Burden System Archetype", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Hsueh, Joe with John Sterman, "Under What Conditions Does Employee Ownership Work? A Model of Ownership Structure and High Performance Work System", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Hu, Bo with Hans-Rolf Vetter, "A System Dynamics Model of Individual Patterns and Strategies for Labor Market Reintegration", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Huang, Jinjing with Enda Howley and Jim Duggan, "An Eigenvector Approach for Analysing Linear Feedback Systems", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Huang, Jinjing with Enda Howley and Jim Duggan, "An Extension of Loop Deactivation in the Behavioral Method", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Hwang, Sungjoo with Moonseo Park and Hyun-Soo Lee, "A Dynamic Approach for Evaluating the Validity of Mortgage Lending Policies in Korean Housing Market", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Jiang, Jie with Jun Li and Xu Honggang, "System Dynamics Model for Transportation Infrastructure Investment and Cultural Heritage Tourism Development", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - John, Klaus, "The Current Debt Crisis - A System Dynamics Analysis", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Kazari, Hessam with Shahab Poshtkouhi and Ali Hassanpoor, "Investigating through ISI Papers Published in Iran and Their Qualities Using Dynamic Approach", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Kazemi, Reza with Masoud Tavazoei, Nikrooz Nasr and Ali Mashayekhi, "An Investigation on The Process of Modification of Subsidy Policy", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Khosla, Karan with Ashok Khosla, "Raising the Quality of Human Life - A Least Cost Route to Reducing Carbon Emissions: Insights from a System Dynamics Model", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Killingsworth, William with Stephen Speciale and Nelson Martin, "Using System Dynamics to Estimate Reductions in Lifecycle Costs Through Investments in Improved Reliability", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Killingsworth, William with Stephen Speciale and Nelson Martin, "The Role of Overhaul in Reducing Lifecycle Costs and Maximizing the Return on Investments to Improve Reliability", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Kim, Dong-Hwan, "Understanding System Dynamics with Eastern Philosophy", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Kim, Jong-Hoon, "HIV Transmissions by Stage under Dynamic Sexual Partnerships", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Kim, Young-Pyo, "Eastern Thought and Systems Thinking", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Kopainsky, Birgit with Pablo Pirnay-Dummer and Stephen Alessi, "Automated Assessment of Learners' Understanding in Complex Dynamic Systems", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Kunc, Martin with Lorenzo Andrade, "Fishing Industry Dynamics: Is fish farming sustainable? An Exploratory Study of the Chilean Salmon Industry", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Kwak, Sangman with Miae Kwak and Sangjin Lee, "A Simulation System for HPAI Diseases Control", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Labedz, Chester with John Gray and James Thompson, "Dynamics of Lean Accounting Innovation on Future Performance: May "Accelerated" Accounting Lead Astray?", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Lee, Eunkyu with Ji-Young An and Dong-Hwan Kim, "Policy Agenda Setting Process and Causal Map Analysis: a case of the Green Growth in Korea", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Lee, Lynette with Mark Heffernan and Geoff McDonnell, "Understanding the dynamics of planning and providing accommodation services for people with Intellectual Disability", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Lee, Young, "Modeling Causes and Impacts of Greenhouse Gas Emission in a City", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Lee, Young with Lianjun An and Daniel Connors, "Controlling Workforce in Response to Demand Disturbances in Services Supply Chains", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Lei, Kampeng with Shek Kiu Chan, Jing Cao and Shaoqi Zhou, "Modeling and Simulation of Ecological Footprint of Macao", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Lektauers, Arnis with Jekabs Trusins and Inese Trusina, "A Conceptual Framework for Dynamic Modeling of Sustainable Development for Local Government in Latvia", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Lerch, Christian with Gregor Selinka, "Dynamics of Business Models - Long-ranging Impact Assessment of Business Models in the Capital Goods Industry", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Li, Anson with Kambiz Maani, "Dynamic Decision-Making, Learning and Mental Models", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Liao, Yi-Wen, "Impacts of Corporate IT Investment Strategies on Operational Performance Based on Intellectual Capital Framework", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Lounsbury, David with Ralph Levine, "Using Dynamics Modeling to Promote Effective Tobacco Treatment Practices in Community-Based Primary Care Settings", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Mahato, Braj with Stephen Ogunlana, "Conflict dynamics in a dam construction project: A case study", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Mai, Thanh with Kambiz Maani, "Systems thinking for sustainable tourism in the Cat Ba Biosphere Reserve of Viet Nam", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29
      - Mashayekhi, Ali with Soheil Ghili, "System Dynamics Problem Definition as an Evolutionary Process Using Ambiguity Concept", 2010 July 25-2010 July 29